New York StateWide Senior Action Council; Records apap111
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Administrative Records, 1975-1997; 1; 1.74 cubic ft.
  - Rural Senior Health Organizing Project, 1988-1991; 1.6; 0.37 cubic ft.
    - Rural Senior Health Organizing Project, Administrative Records, 1986-1988 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Records), Folder 37)
    - Rural Senior Health Organizing Project, Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Records), Folder 38)
    - Quarterly Report, Campaign for Human Development, Quarter 1, 1988 September 15-1988 December 14 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Records), Folder 39)
    - Quarterly Report, CHD, Quarter 2, 1988 December 16-1989 March 15 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Records), Folder 40)
    - Quarterly Report, CHD, Quarter 3, 1889 March 15-1989 June 14 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Records), Folder 41)
    - Quarterly Report, CHD, Quarter 4, 1989 June 15-1989 September 14 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Records), Folder 42)
    - Quarterly Report, CHD, Quarter 1, 1989 September 15-1989 December 14 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Records), Folder 43)
    - Quarterly Report, CHD, Quarter 2, 1989 December 15-1990 March 14 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Records), Folder 44)
    - Quarterly Report, CHD, Quarter 3, 1990 March 15-1990 June 14 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Records), Folder 45)
    - Quarterly Report, CHD, Quarter 4, 1990 June 15-1990 September 14 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Records), Folder 46)
    - Year End Summary, CHD, 1990 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Records), Folder 47)
- Correspondence, 1982-1984; 2; 0.17 cubic ft.
  These records include the correspondence sent and received by Michael Burgess, Executive Director of NYSSAC during this period. Documents include personal letters, intra-organization correspondence, and correspondence with notables such as State Senator Hugh Farley; Director of State Executive Services, Tonio Burgos; Assembly Speaker Stanley Fink; Assemblyman Paul Harenberg; Executive Deputy Secretary of State, James N. Baldwin; and cartoons and letters by local newspaper cartoonist, Charles Ferraro. The series also holds responses to the Public Services Commission's Energy Conservation Survey and correspondence on the grassroots promotional campaign, Savingpower, supporting the Home Insulation and Energy Conservation Act (HIECA).
  - Correspondence, Outgoing, 1982-1983 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 48)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing, 1984 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 49)
  - Correspondence, Received, 1982-1983 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 50)
  - Correspondence, Received, 1984 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 51)
  - Draft Correspondence to Politicians, 1984 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 52)
  - Intra-NYSSAC, 1982-1983 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 53)
  - Public Service Commission Energy Conservation Survey, 1984 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 54)
  - Public Service Commission Program, 1984 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 55)
- Publications, 1977-1981; 1983-2000; 3; 1.5 cubic ft.
  These records contain informational material published by the New York StateWide Senior Action Council in the form of guides, booklets and ephemera. Topics such as community services for senior citizens, Medicare, and consumer issues are addressed. The series includes, NYSSAC's Annual Report for 2000, a position paper against HEAP transfer and, notably, both the Sentinel newsletter (1992-1996) and the Senior Action newspaper (1977-1981, 1983-1994, 1996-2000).
  - Annual Report, 2000 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 1)
  - Bumper Stickers/Membership Cards, Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 2)
  - Guide to Senior Programs, 1999 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 3)
  - Guide to Senior Programs, 2000-2001 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 4)
  - Home Energy Audit Request Slip, 1984 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 5)
  - Informational Brochures, Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 6)
  - Lifetime Legislative Award Honoring Paul Harenberg, 1997 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 7)
  - NYSSAC, Brochure and Priorities, 1985-1986 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 8)
  - Patients' Rights Alert, 1991 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 9)
  - Position Paper Against HEAP Transfer, 1984 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 10)
  - Proposed Patients' Bill of Rights, Media Release, Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 11)
  - Public Service Commission Utility Rates Mailings, 1984 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 12)
  - Originals, 3.13
    - StateWide Sentinel, Monthly Newsletter, 1992 September-1992 December (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 13)
    - StateWide Sentinel, Monthly Newsletter, 1993 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 14)
      Lacking issues for March, July, September.
    - StateWide Sentinel, Monthly Newsletter, 1994 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 15)
      Lacking issue November-December.
    - StateWide Sentinel, Monthly Newsletter, 1995 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 16)
      Lacking issue January-February.
    - StateWide Sentinel, Monthly Newsletter, 1996 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 17)
      Lacking issues for February, July, December.
  - Preservation Photocopies, 3.14
    - Senior Action, January/April, May/August, 1977 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 18)
    - Senior Action, January/March, September-December, 1978 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 19)
    - Senior Action, 1979 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 20)
    - Senior Action, January, April-June, October, 1980 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 21)
    - Senior Action, January-August, 1981 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 22)
    - Senior Action, 1983 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 23)
    - Senior Action, 1984 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 24)
    - Senior Action, 1985 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 25)
    - Senior Action, 1986 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 1)
    - Senior Action, 1987 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 2)
    - Senior Action, 1988 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 3)
    - Senior Action, 1989 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 4)
    - Senior Action, 1990 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 5)
    - Senior Action, June, September/October, 1991 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 6)
    - Senior Action, January/February, July/August, 1992 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 7)
  - Originals in New Format, 3.15
    - Senior Action, Winter, 1994 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 8)
    - Senior Action, Winter, Spring, Summer and "Special Edition", 1996 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 9)
    - Senior Action, "Special Double Issue" December/January, February, April, May, September, October, 1997 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 10)
    - Senior Action, May/June, September, 1998 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 11)
    - Senior Action, April/May, August, "Special Edition", 1999 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 12)
    - Senior Action, March, July/August, 2000 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 13)
  - Senior Action Originals, 3.16
    - Senior Action, 1977 January-April; 1977 May-August (Oversize 3)
    - Senior Action, 1978 January-March; 1978 September-December (Oversize 3)
    - Senior Action, 1979 (Oversize 3)
    - Senior Action, 1980 January; 1980 April-June; 1980 October (Oversize 3)
    - Senior Action, 1981 January-August (Oversize 3)
    - Senior Action, 1983 (Oversize 3)
    - Senior Action, 1984 (Oversize 3)
    - Senior Action, 1985 (Oversize 4)
    - Senior Action, 1986 (Oversize 4)
    - Senior Action, 1987 (Oversize 4)
    - Senior Action, 1988 (Oversize 4)
    - Senior Action, 1989 (Oversize 4)
    - Senior Action, 1990 (Oversize 4)
    - Senior Action, 1991 June; 1991 September-October (Oversize 4)
    - Senior Action, 1992 January-February; 1992 July-August (Oversize 4)
- Subject Files, 1974-1979; 1983-1999; 4; 9.58 cubic ft.
  These records, located within the following sub-series, comprise the base of information used by NYSSAC on issues important to senior citizens and NYSSAC's role as senior advocates.
  Arranged by subject
  - Health Care and Medicare, 1983-1998; 4.1; 6.79 cubic ft.
    These records, which constitute the bulk of the collection, consist of informational and issue files relating to health care topics affecting seniors in New York State. Significant topics addressed include Medicare, Medicaid, Medigap, Long-Term Care, Nursing Homes, DRG (Diagnosis-Related Groups), PROs (Peer-Review Organizations), HMO (Health Maintenance Organizations), the IPRO (Island Peer Review Organization), and others. Files hold information on state and federal health care legislation, the campaign for a national health care system in 1992-1993, the fight for prescription drug coverage for seniors in the state (EPIC) in 1986, and other issues. They include testimonies given before legislative bodies, reports, articles, booklets, legislative bulletins, memorandums, manuals, training material, and correspondence on various topics.
    - AARP Bulletin, 1989 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
    - AARP PRONet, 1988 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
    - AARP Reports on PRO (Peer Review Organization) Reform, 1988 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
    - AARP Reports on PRO Reform, 1988 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
    - Action for Primary Care Legislation, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
    - Advocates for Medicare Assignment meeting, 1989 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
    - Alliance for Aging Research: Report on Home Care, Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
    - Alzheimer's Disease, "Where to go For Help", NYC Department for the Aging, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
    - Amsterdam Hospital Medicare Case, Information Packet, 1986 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
    - Appointment of Dr. Mark Chassen, NY State Health Commissioner, 1991 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
    - Assisted Living Position Paper, 1991 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
    - Association of Area Agencies on the Aging, 1993 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
    - Best Practices in Geriatric Care, 1994 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
    - Blue Cross/Blue Shield Rate Hike, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
    - Blue Cross/Blue Shield Restructuring, 1999 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
    - BNA (Bureau of National Affairs) Health Care Policy Reports, 1996 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
    - Brookdale Foundation Medicaid File, Bulletins, 1988-1990 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
    - Brookdale Foundation Medicare File, Training Material, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
    - California Medical Review: Premature Discharge Study, 1984-1986 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
    - California Medical Review: Premature Discharge Study, Appendices, 1984-1986 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
    - CALS (Community Action for Legal Services), 1989 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
    - Campaign for Quality and Choice in Managed Health Care, 1995 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
    - Campaign for Quality and Choice in Managed Health Care, 1995 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
    - Campaign for Quality and Choice in Managed Health Care, Copy of NY State Senate Bill 4188, 1995 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
    - Capital District Medical Consumers Association, Certificate of Incorporation, Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
    - Capital District Senior Health Services Bureau, 1988 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
    - Capital District Senior Health Services Bureau, 1989 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
    - Center for Medicare Advocacy Waiver of Liability, 1996 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
    - CHCF (Council on Health Care Financing), 1988 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 29)
    - CHCF Health Planning Study, Presentations and Staff Report, 1988 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 30)
    - CHCF Health Planning Study, Profiles and By-laws of Health Systems Agencies, 1988 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 31)
    - CHIC (Consumer Health Information Center) Nursing Home Directory, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 32)
    - Children's Health Care Campaign, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 33)
    - Children's Health Plan (CHP) and Pre-need Materials, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 34)
    - Coalition for Primary Care Legislation, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 35)
    - Coalition to Save Home Care, 1991 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 36)
    - Coalition to Save Medicare, 1995-1996 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 37)
    - Cobble Hill Nursing Home vs. Henry & Warren Corp., Amici Curiae Brief by NY Lawyers for the Public Interest, 1985-1989 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 38)
    - COBRA Health Insurance, 1986 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 39)
    - Committee for Injured Infants' Rights, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 40)
    - Committee for Quality Health Care, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 41)
    - Committee for Quality Health Care, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 42)
    - Committee for Quality Health Care, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 43)
    - Congressional Candidate Medicare Surveys, 1998 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 44)
    - Consumer Advocates' Meeting with Mark Chassen, 1991 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 45)
    - Consumer Choice Alliance for Long Term Care, Draft, ca. 1994 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 46)
    - Department of Health, "Do Not Resuscitate" Guidelines, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
    - Department of Health, Health Care Financing Administration, Guidelines and Forms, 1986-1987 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
    - Department of Health, Health Care Financing Administration, Guidelines and Forms, 1988-1989 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
    - Department of Health, Hospital Code Amendments, 1988 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
    - Department of Health, Hospital Code Guidelines, 1988 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
    - Department of Health, Memo on Health Facilities, 1987 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
    - Department of Health, Memos on Mandatory Medicare Assignment, 1991 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
    - Department of Health, Task Force on Long-Term Care Financing, Public Hearing, 1996 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
    - Department of Health, Task Force on Long-Term Care Financing, Public Hearing Testimonies, 1996 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
    - Department of Social Services Directive on Treatment of Medicaid Trust Funding, 1992 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
    - Directory of Adult Care Facilities in NYS, 1989 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
    - Discharge Planning, News Clippings, 1989 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
    - Discretionary Trust Packet, "Take Me to Your Lawyer", for Families of the Disabled, 1991 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
    - DRG (Diagnosis Related Groups) Action Information, 1985-1987 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
    - DRG Action Information, 1985-1987 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
    - DRG News Clippings, 1987 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
    - DRG Discharge Review Planning, 1990 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17-18)
    - DRG Discharge Studies, 1987 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
    - DRG Education Project, 1990 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
    - DRG Monitoring Committee, 1987 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
    - DRG/PPS (Prospective Payment System) Action Material, 1986-1987 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
    - DRG/PPS News Clippings and Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23-25)
    - DRG/PPS Cases, 1986-1987 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
    - DRG/PPS Cases and Testimony, 1986 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
    - DRG Steering Committee, 1989 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
    - DRG Strategy Group, 1989-1990 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 29-31)
    - DRG Strategy Group, Legal Support Unit Memos, 1983-1986 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 32)
    - DRG Strategy Group, Legal Support Unit Memos, 1987-1988 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 33)
    - DRG Supporting Publications, 1989-1995 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 34)
    - DRG Training Manual, 1986 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 35)
    - Eastern Paralyzed Veteran's Association Summit, 1995 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 36)
    - EISEP (Expanded In-home Services for the Elderly Program) Information, 1987-1990 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 37)
    - Empire Blue Cross/Blue Shield Rate Filing Narrative Summary, 1995 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 38)
    - Empire Blue Cross/Blue Shield Rate Increase Legislation, 1995 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 39)
    - Empire State Medical, Scientific and Educational Foundation Advisory Committee, 1988 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
    - EPIC (Elderly Pharmaceutical Insurance Coverage Program) Advisory Committee, 1992 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
    - EPIC, Information Packets, 1986 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
    - EPIC, Legislation, 1992 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
    - ERISA (Employee Retirement Income Security Act), Preemption, 1993 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
    - Family and Medical Leave Act, 1991 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
    - Friends and Relatives of the Institutionalized Aged (FRIA), 1990 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
    - Governor Cuomo's Health Care Message, 1993 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
    - Governor Cuomo's Revised Long Term Care Access Bill, 153R, 1994 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
    - Governors' Association (National Governors' Association) Proposal on Medicaid, 1996 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
    - Greater New York Hospital Association Memo, 1988 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
    - HCFA (Health Care Financing Administration) Medicare Publications, 1995 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
    - HCFA Policy Correspondence, 1987 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
    - Health Care Agents and Proxies Bill #76 RR, 1990 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
    - Health Care Campaign Surveys, 1988 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
    - Health Care News Clippings, 1991 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
    - Health Care News Clippings, 1996 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
    - Health Care For All, Advocacy Group, 1989 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
    - Health Care For All, Bulletins and Background Material, 1988-1991 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
    - Health Care For All, Campaign, 1989 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
    - Health Care For All, Campaign, 1993 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
    - Health Care For All, Campaign Structure, 1991 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
    - Health Care For All, Meeting, 1994 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
    - Health Care For All, Patients' Rights Fund, 1993 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
    - Health Care Reform, 1993 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
    - Health Care Reform, 1994 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
    - Health Care Reform Debate, 1992-1993 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
    - Health Care Reform, Legislative Action Materials, 1992 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
    - Health Care Surveillance Work Group, 1989 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 29)
    - Health Data Design Committee, 1992 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 30)
    - Health Financing Advisory Group, 1988 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 31)
    - Health Issues File, 1987 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 32)
    - Health Systems Agencies Information, 1988 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 33)
    - Hearing Aid Dispensing, Assembly Bill 1175A, 1995 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 34)
    - Hearing Aid Legislation, 1995-1996 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 35)
    - Hill-Burton Program Information, 1985-1988 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 36)
    - HMO (Heath Maintenance Organization) Community Ratings, 1992 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 37)
    - Home Care Assessment Tool, (HARRI), 1993 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 38)
    - Home Care for the Functionally Impaired, 1986 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 39)
    - Hospital Admissions Information, 1992 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 40)
    - Hospital Association of NY, Report, 1989 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 41)
    - Hospital Information, 1986-1989 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 42)
    - Hospital Patient Rights, 1994 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 43)
    - "How to Talk About Health Care", Arnold Bennett, 1990 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 44)
    - Human Services Summit, 1989 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 45)
    - IPRO (Island Peer Review Organization) Committee Meetings, 1990 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 46)
    - IPRO, DRG Strategy Group, 1990 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 47)
    - IPRO Medicare Administrative Memos, 1990 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 48)
    - IPRO Medicare Administrative Memos, 1992-1993 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 49)
    - IPRO Outreach, 1991 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
    - IPRO Problems/Complaints, 1990 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
    - Legal Services for the Elderly, Medicaid/Home Care, 1992 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
    - Letter From National Council of Senior Citizens, Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
    - Long Term Care Access, 1992-1993 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
    - Long Term Care Access, 1994 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
    - Long Term Care Access Reform, 1992 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
    - Long Term Care Access Reform, 1993 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
    - Long Term Care Access Reform, 1994 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
    - Long Term Care Access Reform, Support Material, 1993 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
    - Long Term Care Access, Task Force, 1992 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
    - Long Term Care Alliance Mailing Lists, 1994 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
    - Long Term Care Assessment Consolidation Project, 1993 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
    - Long Term Care Assessment Seminar, Transcript, 1994 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
    - Long Term Care Campaign, 1988 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
    - Long Term Care Campaign, 1990 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
    - Long Term Care Campaign Action, 1989-1991 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
    - Long Term Care Campaign, Correspondence to Governor Guidelines, Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
    - Long Term Care Information, 1990-1994 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
    - Long Term Care Initiatives in Massachusetts and New Jersey, 1994 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
    - Long Term Care Insurance News Clipping, 1993 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
    - Long Term Care Public Policy Issues, 1992-1994 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
    - Long Term Care Reform Conference, 1994 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
    - Long Term Care Services, 1993 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
    - Long Term Care Single Payer Plan Reform, 1991-1992 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
    - Long Term Care Strategic Development Committee, 1995 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
    - Managed Access to Aging Services (MAAS) Proposal, 1991 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
    - Mandatory Medicare Assignment, Bill A. 3500, 1990 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
    - Mandatory Medicare Assignment, Bill A. 3500, 1991 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 29)
    - Mandatory Medicare Assignment, Bill A. 12304, NYS Supreme Court Case, 1992 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 30)
    - Mandatory Medicare Assignment Campaign, 1987-1988 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 31)
    - Mandatory Medicare Assignment Campaign, 1988-1990 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 32)
    - Mandatory Medicare Assignment Campaign, 1990 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 33)
    - Mandatory Medicare Assignment Enforcement, 1989-1990 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 34)
    - Mandatory Medicare Assignment Public Hearings, 1987 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 35)